Guide to the Joseph L. Fisher papers, 1962-1991
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 1: Academic Career/Government Appointments, 1962-1991
  - JLF PERSONAL HUMAN ENVIRONMENT CENTER (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - JLF PERSONAL MITRE (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - NAMES PLUS ADDRESSES (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - JLF PERSONAL NATIONAL KIDNEY FOUNDATION (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - JLF PERSONAL OBERLIN COLLEGE (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - PERSONAL (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - PERSONAL MISC (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - JLF PERSONAL POPULATION REFERENCE BUREAU (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - JLF PERSONAL RESOURCES FOR THE FUTURE (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - JLF PERSONAL ROBB CAMPAIGN - ENERGY WORKING GROUP (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - JLF PERSONAL SOCIETY FOR INTERNATIONAL DEVELOPMENT (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - JLF PERSONAL 10TH DISTRICT (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - JLF PERSONAL UNITARIAN UNIVERSALIST ASSOCIATION (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - UNITARIAN UNIVERSALIST ASSOCIATION (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - JLF PERSONAL WMA PLUS A (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - NEWS CLIPPINGS (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - ALASKA THE DEVELOPMENT OF OUR ARCTIC FRONTIER (PART 1) (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - ALASKA THE DEVELOPMENT OF OUR ARCTIC FRONTIER (PART 1) (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - PROBLEMS IN THE STUDY OF ECONOMIC GROWTH (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - RESOURCES CONSERVATION IN THE UNIVERSITY SOCIAL SCIENCE CURRICULUM (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - CONCEPTS IN REGIONAL ECONOMIC DEVELOPMENT (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - IMPLICATIONS OF THE NEW DEVELOPMENT IN ENERGY FOR THE AMERICAN ECONOMY (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - THE ADEQUACY OF RESOURCES FOR ECONOMIC GROWTH IN THE UNITED STATES (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - CONSERVATION FOR MORE AND MORE PEOPLE (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - OUR RESOURCE SITUATION: PUBLIC POLICY AND INDIVIDUAL RESPONSIBILITY AUGUST, 1960 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - A FRAMEWORK FOR WILDERNESS RESEARCH (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - RESOURCE POLICIES AND ADMINISTRATION FOR THE FUTURE (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - NATURAL RESOURCES PROJECTIONS AND THEIR CONTRIBUTION TO TECHNOLOGICAL PLANING (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - THE MULTIPLE USE OF OUR NATURAL RESOURCES (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - RESOURCES IN AMERICA'S FUTURE (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - NATURAL RESOURCES: TRENDS, POLICIES AND ADMINISTRATION (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - PROFILES OF THE FUTURE: RESOURCE PROTECTI0NS (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - WORLD PROSPECTS FOR NATURAL RESOURCES (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - NOTES ON RESOURCES EDUCATION (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - RESOURCES POLICIES FOR A GREAT SOCIETY (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - INTERIM REPORT OF THE OIL SHALE ADVISORY BOARD (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - RESOURCES IN 1980 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - THE RELATIONSHIP OF MATERIAL RESOURCES AND POPULATION TO ECONOMIC AND SOCIAL DEVELOPMENT (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - REFLECTIONS ON SOME PROBLEMS OF THE NATIONAL CAPITAL REGION (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - COPING WITH CRISES IN THE NATURAL RESOURCES (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - REFLECTIONS ON THE FORMULATION OF REGIONAL POLICY (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - OUR GREATEST GAMBLE (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - NATURAL RESOURCES TRENDS AND THEIR IMPLICATIONS FOR THE ROCKY MOUNTAIN REGION (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - NATURAL RESOURCES AND THE FUTURE OF MAN (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - THE JOB OF THE CONGRESSMAN 1966 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - NATURAL RESOURCE PROBLEMS AND TVA (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - PERSPECTIVES ON NATURAL RESOURCES AND HUMAN RESOURCES (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - THE PUBLIC CONCERN FOR CONSERVATION (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - ENVIRONMENTAL QUALITY AND URBAN LIVING (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - THE NATURAL ENVIRONMENT (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - EVERYONE'S WAR (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - LIMITS ON THE EXPLOITATION OF NATURAL RESOURCES (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - ENERGY NEEDS: EXPANDING OUR RESOURCES (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - NEW PERSPECTIVES ON CONSERVATI0N (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - ECONOMIC AND SOCIAL ASPECTS OF ENVIRONMENTAL ENHANCEMENT (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - SOUND RESOURCES DECISIONS: WHAT KIND OF FORESTERS WILL BE NEEDED? (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - EFFECTS OF POPULATION GROWTH ON NATURAL RESOURCES AND THE ENVIRONMENT (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - ENVIRONMENT COMES IN REGIONAL PACKAGES (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - A LARGER FUTURE FOR SOIL CONSERVATION (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - AN EXPANDING FUTURE FOR SOIL CONSERVATION (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - DIMENSIONS OF THE ENVIRONMENTAL CRISIS (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - ENVIRONMENTAL POLLUTION AND THE FUTURE OF MAN'S EARTH (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - POLICIES FOR BALANCE GROWTH (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - IMPACT OF POPULATION ON RESOURCES AND THE ENVIRONMENT (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - CONSERVATION AS RESEARCH, POLICY AND ACTION (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - RESOURCES FOR BUSINESS (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - ECONOMIC DEVELOPMENT AND ENVIRONMENTAL PROTECTION: TECHNOLOGY AND PUBLIC POLICY (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - FUTURE ENERGY DEMAND AND ITS EFFECTS ON THE ENVIRONMENT (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - EPILOGUE TO "THE NO - GROWTH SOCIETY" (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - STATEMENT: PROCEEDINGS OF THE WESTERN GOVERNOR'S CONFERENCE (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - EL PROBLEMA DE LOS RECURSOS NO RENOVABLES (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - A SEARCH FOR CONSENSUS (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - A PERSONAL REMINISCENCE (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - NON - RENEWABLE NATURAL RESOURCE AVAILABILITY (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - ENERGY CHOICES AND PUBLIC POLICY (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - THE EFFECTS OF POPULATION GROWTH ON RESOURCE ADEQUACY AND QUALITY (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - RESOURCE FOR THE FUTURE (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - PERSPECTIVES ON THE UNITARIAN UNIVERALIST FUTURE (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - KEY NOTE ADDRESS THE IMPORTANCE OF THE BUILT ENVIRONMENT TO THE QUALITY OF AMERICAN LIFE (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - PRESERVING THE POTOMAC (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - PERSPECTIVE FROM PUBLIC INTEREST GROUPS (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - ENERGY POLICY IN PERSPECTIVE - SOLUTIONS, PROBLEMS, AND PROSPECTS (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - HUMAN SERVICES IN A TIME OF DIMINISHED RESOURCES (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - OUR GROUNDWATER IS GENERALLY GOOD (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - THE FUTURE OF ARLINGTON: THE YEAR 2000 AND BEYOND (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - VIRGINIA ALTERNATIVES FOR THE 1990's (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - ON UMBRELLA'S AND HUMAN SERVICES IN VIRGINIA (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - THE FUTURE OF NORTHERN VIRGINIA: CHALLENGE AND REALIZATION (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - TOWARD A NORTHERN VIRGINIA STYLE (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - FORMAL MECHANISMS: HELPING THE GOVERNOR TO MANAGE (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - BEYOND DISTRUST: BUILDING BRIDGES BETWEEN CONGRESS AND THE EXECUTIVE (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - FISHER JOSEPH L WW II SCRAPBOOK (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - FISHER SCRAPBOOK BUILD UP TO PRIMARY 1972 - 74 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - FISHER SCRAPBOOK (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - FISHER SCRAPBOOK NOVEMBER 6, 1974 - FEBRUARY 14, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - FISHER SCRAPBOOK 1975 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - FISHER SCRAPBOOK 1975 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - FISHER SCRAPBOOK (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - FISHER SCRAPBOOK NOVEMBER, 1976 - MAY 1977 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - FISHER SCRAPBOOK 1977 - 78 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - FISHER SCRAPBOOK JUNE, 1978 - JANUARY, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - FISHER SCRAPBOOK 1979 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - FISHER SCRAPBOOK NOVEMBER 1979 - AUGUST 1980 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - FISHER SCRAPBOOK SEPTEMBER - DECEMBER 1980 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - FISHER SCRAPBOOK JANUARY 1981 - JANUARY 1982 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - FISHER SCRAPBOOK 1982 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - FISHER SCRAPBOOK (Box 49, Folder 9)
- Series 2: U.S. House of Representatives, 1974-1981
  Papers relate to Fisher's political career in U.S. House of Representatives (1974-1981). The materials cover the years 1974-1981 and include: correspondence, speeches, press releases, reports, newsclippings, issue papers, testimony, statements, questionnaires, background publications, guidelines, charts, and legislation.
  - 96th CONGRESS - 2nd SESSION JOHN L. NORMAN - GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE. (Folder 1, Box 1)
  - 96th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER STATEMENTS. (Folder 2, Box 1)
  - 96th CONGRESS - 2nd SESSION FISHER STATEMENTS. (Folder 3, Box 1)
  - 96th CONGRESS 1ST SESSION - CO - SIGNED LETTERS, DEAR COLLEAGUES. (Folder 4, Box 1)
  - 96th CONGRESS - 2nd SESSION C0 - SIGNED LETTERS, DEAR COLLEAGUES. (Folder 5, Box 1)
  - 96th CONGRESS - 1ST SESSION - NEWS RELEASES. (Folder 6, Box 1)
  - 96th CONGRESS - 2nd SESSION - NEWS RELEASES. (Folder 7, Box 1)
  - 96th CONGRESS - 1ST SESSION - TESTIMONY. (Folder 8, Box 1)
  - 96th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION - AMENDMENTS. (Folder 9, Box 1)
  - 95TH CONGRESS - 1ST SESSION - FISHER BILL H.R. 2683 - ADDING POPULATION - DENSITY FACTOR TO DEFINITION OF URBAN COUNTY- BANKING, FINANCE PLUS URBAN AFFAIRS. (Folder 1, Box 2)
  - NONRESIDENT INCOME TAXATION HR 10116 AND HR 11303. (Folder 2, Box 2)
  - 95th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION - FISHER BILL H.RES.12 - PERMIT EMPLOYEES OF HOUSE TO CONTRIBUTE THROUGH PAYROLL WITHHOLDING - HOUSE ADMINISTRATION. (Folder 3, Box 2)
  - 95th CONGRESS - 2ND SESSION - FISHER BILL H.R. 1536 - ESTABLISHED WITHIN THE DEPT. OF STATE AN ASSISTANT SECRETARY FOR CLAIMS AGAINST FOREIGN MINISTERS AND DIPLOMATS AND AWARDS JUST COMPENSATION FOR SUCH CLAIMS. (Folder 4, Box 2)
  - 95TH CONGRESS - 1ST SESSION - FISHER BILL H.R.936 - TO REQUIRE A REFUND VALUE FOR CERTAIN BEVERAGE CONTAINERS - INTERSTATE AND FOREIGN COMMERCE. (Folder 5, Box 2)
  - 95TH CONGRESS - 1ST SESSION - FISHER BILL H.R. 3645 - FEDERAL CIVILIAN AND POSTED SERVICE EMPLOYEES RIGHTS TO - POST OFFICE AND CIVIL SERVICE PARTICIPATION IN POLITICAL PROCESS. (Folder 6, Box 2)
  - 95TH CONGRESS - 2ND SESSION - FISHER BILL H.R. 4620 - SPECIAL ALLOWANCES TO CERTAIN PHYSICIANS EMPLOYED BY U.S. - POSTAL OFFICE AND CIVIL SERVICE. (Folder 7, Box 2)
  - 95th CONGRESS - 1ST SESSION - FISHER BILL H.R. 955 - GRANTS FOR THE CONSTRUCTION OF BIKEWAYS - PUBLIC WORK PLUS TRANSPORTATION. (Folder 8, Box 2)
  - 95TH CONGRESS - 1ST SESSION - GENERAL. (Folder 9, Box 2)
  - 95TH CONGRESS - 1ST SESSION GENERAL. (Folder 10, Box 2)
  - 95TH CONGRESS - 2nd SESSION GENERAL. (Folder 11, Box 2)
  - 95TH CONGRESS - 2nd SESSION - GENERAL NEWS RELEASES. (Folder 12, Box 2)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1ST SESSION H.R. 2449 - PROHIBIT INCREASE IN THE PRICE OF FOOD STAMPS - AGRICULTURE. (Folder 13, Box 2)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1ST SESSION, FISHER BILL H.R. 8552 GIFTS TO NATIONAL ARBORETUM - AGRICULTURE. (Folder 14, Box 2)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1ST SESSION, FISHER BILL H.R. 8778 - HUMAN TREATMENT OF ANIMALS - AGRICULTURE. (Folder 15, Box 2)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1ST SESSION FISHER BILL H.RES, 56 - DISAPPROVAL OF BUDGET DEFERRAL OF HUD PLANNING PROGRAM - APPROPRIATES. (Folder 16, Box 2)
  - 1976 FISHER BILL RE: WILSON RECOMPUTATION BILL - ARMED FORCES. (Folder 17, Box 2)
  - 94th C0NGRESS - 1ST SESSION FISHER BILL H.R. 9142 RECOMPUTATION OF MILITARY RETIRED PAY- ARMED SERVICES. (Folder 18, Box 2)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 2ND SESSION FISHER BILL H.R. 14341 - PROHIBITION OF UNIONS IN THE ARMED FORCES - ARMED FORCES. (Folder 19, Box 2)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER BILL - H.R. 4029 - MAINTAIN COMMISSARY STORES - ARMED SERVICES. (Folder 1, Box 3)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 2nd SESSION FISHER BILL - H.R. 13005 - NATIONAL CONDOMINIUM AND TENANTS RIGHTS ACT - B,C AND H. (Folder 2, Box 3)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 2nd SESSION FISHER BILL - H.R. 13934 - G. W. UNIVERSITY CHARTER - DISTRICT OF COLUMBIA. (Folder 3, Box 3)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER BILL - H.R. 15434 - WATER RATE STRUCTURE - D.C. AND PUBLIC WORKS COMMITTEES. (Folder 4, Box 3)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER BILL - H.R. 6360 - METRO FINANCING - DISTRICT OF COLUMBIA. (Folder 5, Box 3)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER BILL - H.R. 10440 - COMMISSION TO STUDY FEDERAL PAYMENT TO D.C. - DISTRICT OF COLUMBIA. (Folder 6, Box 3)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 2nd SESSION FISHER BILL - H.R. 10798 - D.C. MEDICAL AND DENTAL MANPOWER - DISTRICT OF COLUMBIA. (Folder 7, Box 3)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 2nd SESSION FISHER BILL - H.R. 15518 - AGE DISCRIMINATION IN EMPLOYMENT - EDUCATION AND LABOR. (Folder 8, Box 3)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER BILL - H.R. 8619 - SMALL BUSINESS UNDER OSHA - EDUCATION AND LABOR. (Folder 9, Box 3)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 2nd SESSION FISHER BILL - H.R. 13812 - FEDERAL PROCUREMENT POLICY ACT - GOVT. OPERATIONS. (Folder 10, Box 3)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 2nd SESSION FISHER BILL - H.CON. RES. 744 - IMPACT OF FED. PROPERTY ON LOCAL GOVT. - GOVT. OPERATIONS. (Folder 11, Box 3)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER BILL - H.R. 11108 - INTERESTS ON OVERDUE CONTRACT PAYMENTS - GOVT. OPERATIONS. (Folder 12, Box 3)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 2nd SESSION FISHER BILL - H.R. 14472 - MIHAILOVICH MOVEMENT - HOUSE ADMINISTRATION. (Folder 13, Box 3)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER BILL - H.R. 5543 - AMERICAN FOLK LIFE CENTER - HOUSE ADMINISTRATION. (Folder 14, Box 3)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER BILL - H.R. 9103 - PUBLIC FINANCING OF CONGRESSIONAL CAMPAIGNS - HOUSE ADMINISTRATION. (Folder 15, Box 3)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER BILL - H.R. 136 - WITHHOLDING OF STATE TAX FOR HOUSE EMPLOYEES - HOUSE ADMINISTRATION. (Folder 16, Box 3)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER BILL - H.R. 294 - JOHN MC CORMACK Sr. INTERN PROGRAM - HOUSE ADMINISTRATION. (Folder 17, Box 3)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 2nd SESSION FISHER BILL - H.R. 11875 - POTOMAC NATIONAL RIVER - INTERIOR PLUS INSULAR AFFAIRS. (Folder 18, Box 3)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 2nd SESSION FISHER BILL - H.R. 12850 - NEW RIVER - INTERIOR PLUS INSULAR AFFAIRS. (Folder 19, Box 3)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 2nd SESSION FISHER BILL - H.R. 1228 - BRGGS / BEGICH PEAKS IN ALASKA - INTERIOR PLUS INSULAR AFFAIRS. (Folder 20, Box 3)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER BILL - H.R. 5633 - LAND USE PLANING - INTERI0R PLUS INSULAR AFFAIRS. (Folder 21, Box 3)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER BILL - H.R. 6624 - SHENADOAH WILDERNESS - INTERIOR PLUS INSULAR AFFAIRS. (Folder 22, Box 3)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER BILL - H.R. 6892 SHENANDOOH WILDERNESS - INTERIOR PLUS INSULAR AFFAIRS. (Folder 23, Box 3)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER BILL - H.R. 9222 - MANASSAS NATIONAL BATTLEFIELD PARK - INTERIOR PLUS INSULAR AFFAIRS. (Folder 24, Box 3)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 2nd SESSION FISHER BILL - DIPLOMATIC IMMUNITY BILLS WITH CO - SPONSORS - INTERNATIONAL RELATIONS. (Folder 25, Box 3)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 2nd SESSION FISHER BILL - H.R. 14828 - DIPLOMATIC IMMUNITY - INTERNATIONAL RELATIONS. (Folder 26, Box 3)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 2nd SESSION FISHER BILL - H.R. 15683 PLUS H.R. 15684 - DIPLOMATIC RELATIONS - INTERNATIONAL RELATIONS. (Folder 27, Box 3)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER BILL - H.CON. RES. 351 - SALE OF ARMS TO JORDAN - INTERNATIONAL RELATIONS. (Folder 28, Box 3)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER BILL - H.R. 608 - CALLING AN ATLANTIC CONFERENCE - INTERNATIONAL RELATIONS. (Folder 29, Box 3)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 2nd SESSION FISHER BILL - H.R. 9393 - COMMISSION ON REGULATORY REFORM - INTERSTATE PLSU FOREIGN COMMERCE. (Folder 30, Box 3)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 2nd SESSION FISHER BILL - H.R. 12053 - FRANCHISE PRACTICES - INTERSTATE PLUS FOREIGN COMMERCE. (Folder 31, Box 3)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 2nd SESSION FISHER BILL - H.R. 15610 - RADIO FREQUENCY INTERFERENCE 0 INTERSTATE PLUS FOREIGN COMMERCE. (Folder 32, Box 3)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 2nd SESSION FISHER BILL - H.R. 15627 - LIFE SUPPORT CENTERS ACT - INTERSTATE PLUS FOREIGN COMMERCE. (Folder 33, Box 3)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER BILL - H.R. 3246 - RETURNABLE BEVERAGE CONTAINER ACT OF 1975 - INTERSTATE PLSU FOREIGN COMMERCE. (Folder 34, Box 3)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 2nd SESSION FISHER BILL - H.R. 12178 - RELIEF OF EDWARD J. SHEA - PRIVATE JUDICIARY. (Folder 35, Box 3)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 2nd SESSION FISHER BILL - H.R. 1565 - CONDEMNING MURDERS OF LETELIER PLUS MOFFITT - JUDICIARY. (Folder 36, Box 3)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER BILL - H.R. 2926 - FEDERAL FINANCIAL DISCLOSURE - JUDICIARY PLUS OFF. COND. (Folder 37, Box 3)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 2nd SESSION FISHER BILL - H.R. 3048 - FEDERAL LOBBYING REGISTRATION ACT - JUDICIARY PLUS COND. (Folder 38, Box 3)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER BILL - H.R. 9457 - RELIEF OF RUTH GUILDER - PRIVATE JUDICIARY. (Folder 39, Box 3)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER BILL H.R. 10009 - FINANCIAL DISCLOSURE - JUDICIARY/OFFICIAL CONDUCT. (Folder 1, Box 4)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER BILL H.R. 10478 - RELIEF OF LUISA LAVANDEZ DE ALVAREZ. (Folder 2, Box 4)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER BILL H.J. RES. 254 - ROBERT E. LEE CITIZENSHIP - JUDICIARY. (Folder 3, Box 4)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER BILL H.J. RES. 432 - D.C. REPRESENTATION IN CONGRESS - JUDICIARY. (Folder 4, Box 4)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER BILL H.R. 7498 - FISH AND WILDLIFE SERVICE ADMINISTRATION - MERCHANT MARINE PLUS FISHERIES. (Folder 5, Box 4)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER BILL H.R. 10900 - TINICUM NATIONAL ENVIRONMENTAL CENTER - MERCHANT MARINE PLUS FISHERIES. (Folder 6, Box 4)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 2nd SESSION FISHER BILL H.R. 13641 - HATCH ACT REVISION - POST OFFICE PLUS SERVICE. (Folder 7, Box 4)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 2nd SESSION FISHER BILL H.R. 13933 - ALLOWANCES FOR PHYSICIANS - POST OFFICE PLUS CIVIL SERVICE. (Folder 8, Box 4)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 2nd SESSION FISHER BILL H.R. 14061 - INCREASE CIVIL SERVICE COMMISSION MEMBERSHIP - POST OFFICE PLUS CIVIL SERVICE. (Folder 9, Box 4)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER BILL H.RES. 1238 - CLOSING OF POST OFFICE PLUS CIVIL SERVICE. (Folder 10, Box 4)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 2nd SESSION FISHER BILL H.J.RES. 777 - THOMAS JEFFERSON DAY - POST OFFICE PLUS CIVIL SERVICE. (Folder 11, Box 4)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 2nd SESSION FISHER BILL H.R. 1063 - NATION VOLUNTEER FIREMEN WEEK - POST OFFICE PLUS CIVIL SERVICE. (Folder 12, Box 4)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER BILL H.R. 2660 - CIVIL SERVICE RETIREMENT FOR ARMED FORCES EMPLOYEES - POST OFFICE PLUS CIVIL SERVICE. (Folder 13, Box 4)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER BILL H.R. 2661 - DOD EMPLOYEES UNDER CIVIL SERVICE - POST OFFICE. (Folder 14, Box 4)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER BILL H.R. 3934 - FEDERAL EMPLOYEES POLITICAL ACTIVITIES ACT - POST OFFICE PLUS CIVIL SERVICE. (Folder 15, Box 4)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER BILL H.R. 5350 - FEDERAL EMPLOYEES RELOCATION - POST OFFICE PLUS CIVIL SERVICE. (Folder 16, Box 4)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER BILL H.R. 7604 - RE: CHANGES IN FEDERAL EMPLOYEE HEALTH INSURANCE - POST OFFICE PLUS CIVIL SERVICE. (Folder 17, Box 4)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER BILL H.R. 9440 - EXECUTIVE BRANCH EMPLOYEES PAY COMPARABILITY - POST OFFICE PLUS CIVIL SERVICE. (Folder 18, Box 4)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER BILL H.R. 9994 - COURT LEAVE FPR FEDERAL EMPLOYEES - POST OFFICE PLUS CIVIL SERVICE. (Folder 19, Box 4)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER BILL H.R. 10060 - DISALLOW PRESIDENTS PLAN FOR FEDERAL PAY RAISE - POST OFFICE PLUS CIVIL SERVICE. (Folder 20, Box 4)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER BILL H.R. 10491 - CONGRESSIONAL PAY FREEZE - POST OFFICE PLUS CIVIL SERVICE. (Folder 21, Box 4)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER BILL H.R. 5591 - PUBLIC WORKS CAPITAL DEVELOPMENT - PUBLIC WORKS. (Folder 22, Box 4)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 2nd SESSION FISHER BILL H.R. 12784 - GOVERNMENT ECONOMY PLUS SPENDING REFORM ACT - RULES. (Folder 23, Box 4)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 2nd SESSION FISHER BILL H.R. 1130 - SELECT COMMITTEE ON NUCLEAR PROLIFERATION - RULES. (Folder 24, Box 4)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 2nd SESSION FISHER BILL H.R. 1317 - REMOVE LIMITATIONS ON NUMBER OF CO - SPONSORS RULES. (Folder 25, Box 4)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 2nd SESSION FISHER BILL H.R. 1345 - INVESTIGATIONS BY COMMITTEE ON OFFICIAL CONDUCT - RULES. (Folder 26, Box 4)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 2nd SESSION FISHER BILL H.R. 1436 - EX-MEMBERS PROHIBITED FROM LOBBYING ON HOUSE FLOOR - RULES. (Folder 27, Box 4)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER BILL H.R. 466 - OPEN CONFERENCE COMMITTEE - RULES COMMITTEE. (Folder 28, Box 4)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER BILL H.RES. 496 - SELECT COMMITTEE ON MIA'S - RULES COMMITTEE. (Folder 29, Box 4)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER BILL H.RES. 620 - SELECT COMMITTEE ON ENERGY - RULES. (Folder 30, Box 4)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 2nd SESSION FISHER BILL H.R. 13215 - UNKNOWN REVOLUTIONARY WAR SOLDIER - VETERANS AFFAIRS. (Folder 31, Box 4)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER BILL H.R. 4857 - LIFE INSURANCE FOR VETS WITH SERVICE - CONNECTED DISABILITIES - VETERANS AFFAIRS. (Folder 32, Box 4)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 2nd SESSION FISHER BILL H.R. 13500 - LOBBYING BY PUBLIC CHARITIES - WAYS PLUS MEANS. (Folder 33, Box 4)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 2nd SESSION FISHER BILL H.R. 13890 - RENTERS TAX CREDIT - WAYS PLUS MEANS. (Folder 34, Box 4)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 2nd SESSION FISHER BILL H.R. 15357 - AUTO INSURANCE FOR DIPLOMATS - WAYS PLUS MEANS. (Folder 35, Box 4)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER BILL H.R. 1767 - PROHIBIT OIL TARIFF FOR 90 DAYS - WAYS PLUS MEANS. (Folder 36, Box 4)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER BILL H.R. 3832 - ESTATE TAX ON FARMS - WAYS PLUS MEANS. (Folder 37, Box 4)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER BILL H.R. 7131 - CONDOMINIUM TAX EXEMPTION - WAYS PLUS MEANS. (Folder 38, Box 4)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER BILL H.R. 7694 - NURSING CARE UNDER MEDICARE - WAYS PLUS MEANS. (Folder 39, Box 4)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER BILL H.R. 8021 - LOBBYING BY TAX EXEMPT ORGANIZATIONS - WAYS PLUS MEANS. (Folder 40, Box 4)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER BILL H.R. 8579 - TAXATION OF LEGAL SERVICE FEES - WAYS PLUS MEANS. (Folder 41, Box 4)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER BILL H.R. 9442 - TAX PRIVACY ACT OF '75 - WAYS PLUS MEANS. (Folder 42, Box 4)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER BILL H.R. 9494 - SOCIAL SECURITY CLAIMS PROCEDURES - WAYS PLUS MEANS. (Folder 43, Box 4)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER BILL H.CON. RES. 58 - PROHIBIT OIL TARIFF UNTIL 4/1/75 - WAYS PLUS MEANS. (Folder 44, Box 4)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION FISHER BILL H.CON. RES. 72 - RESOLUTION DISAPPROVING CEILING ON S.S. BENEFITS - WAYS PLUS MEANS. (Folder 45, Box 4)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1975 - 76 FISHER VOTING RECORD. (Folder 46, Box 4)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st AND 2nd SESSION. (Folder 47, Box 4)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 2nd SESSION GENERAL. (Folder 48, Box 4)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 2nd SESSION GENERAL. (Folder 49, Box 4)
  - 94th CONGRESS - 1st SESSION - GENERAL. (Folder 50, Box 4)
  - REFORMS OF CONGRESS. (Folder 1, Box 5)
  - TED TAYLOR SEMINAR HOUSE REFORM SEMINAR. (Folder 2, Box 5)
  - TED TAYLOR SEMINAR CONGRESSIONAL PAY RAISE. (Folder 3, Box 5)
  - 1980 - SELECTED COMMITTEE ON COMMITTEES. (Folder 4, Box 5)
  - COMMITTEE ON COMMITTEES. (Folder 5, Box 5)
  - ETHICS - ISSUE PAPER # 9. (Folder 6, Box 5)
  - WAYS PLUS MEANS COMMITTEE. (Folder 7, Box 5)
  - TAX LEGISLATION. (Folder 8, Box 5)
  - TAXES - MISCELLANEOUS. (Folder 9, Box 5)
  - MISCELLANEOUS TAX LEGISLATION. (Folder 10, Box 5)
  - MISCELLANEOUS TAXES. (Folder 11, Box 5)
  - TAXPAYER SENTIMENT. (Folder 12, Box 5)
  - MISCELLANEOUS TAXES. (Folder 13, Box 5)
  - MISCELLANEOUS TAXES. (Folder 14, Box 5)
  - MISCELLANEOUS TAXES. (Folder 15, Box 5)
  - MISCELLANEOUS TAXES. (Folder 16, Box 5)
  - MISCELLANEOUS TAXES. (Folder 17, Box 5)
  - TAX QUESTIONNAIRE. (Folder 18, Box 5)
  - MISCELLANEOUS TAXES. (Folder 19, Box 5)
  - MISCELLANEOUS TAXES. (Folder 20, Box 5)
  - MISCELLANEOUS TAXES. (Folder 21, Box 5)
  - TAXES - MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE. (Folder 22, Box 5)
  - TAXES - MISCELLANEOUS CORRESPONDENCE. (Folder 23, Box 5)
  - MISCELLANEOUS TAXES. (Folder 1, Box 6)
  - COPIES OF TAX BILL. (Folder 2, Box 6)
  - 1976 WAYS PLUS MEANS TAX CORRESPONDENCE. (Folder 3, Box 6)
  - 1975 - WAYS PLUS MEANS COMMITTEE MISCELLANEOUS TAX ISSUES. (Folder 4, Box 6)
  - TAXES - MISCELLANEOUS ISSUES ( CORRESPONDENCE 1975). (Folder 5, Box 6)
  - 1975 - WAYS PLUS MEANS COMMITTEE MISCELLANEOUS TAX ISSUES. (Folder 6, Box 6)
  - 1975 - WAYS PLUS MEANS COMMITTEE MISCELLANEOUS TAX ISSUES (Folder 7, Box 6)
  - ANTI - INFLATION MATERIAL. (Folder 8, Box 6)
  - ADMINISTRATION TAX PACKAGE. (Folder 9, Box 6)
  - ADMINISTRATION TAX PACKAGE. (Folder 10, Box 6)
  - ADMINISTRATION TAX PACKAGE. (Folder 11, Box 6)
  - ADMINISTRATION TAX PACKAGE. (Folder 12, Box 6)
  - ADMINISTRATION TAX PACKAGE. (Folder 13, Box 6)